buzzerg.com 2018-07-15

# Privacy Policy – BUZZERG

**Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

**Collection of Personal Information**

We may collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and in order to create reports. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. 

We use Google Analytics. It is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it. 

We have implemented the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting features on our website. These tools allow us to review anonymous data regarding the gender, age and interests of website visitors. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site.

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this [Google page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of [buzzerg.com](http://buzzerg.com/) then you may [contact us](http://buzzerg.com/contact-us).
